A Finding Aid to the Burt Chernow Papers, 1930-2002, in the Archives of American Art AAA.cherburt
Archives of American Art
- Photographs, 1950-1997; Series 5; 0.8 Linear feet Boxes 21-23
  - Photographs of the Chernows with Artists (Box 22)
    - Lester Johnson, 1990 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Paul Jenkins, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Gabor Peterdi, circa 1990 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Mary Bauermeister, circa 1992 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Dale Chihuly, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Will Barnet, circa 1995 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Photographs of Artists by Others (Box 22)
    - Abe Ajay, circa 1960; 1980 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Richard Anuszkiewicz, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Arman, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Milton Avery by Lee Sievan, circa 1950 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Mary Bauermeister, circa 1980 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Georges Bracque, circa 1970 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Paul Cadmus, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - John Cage, Nam June Paik, and David Tudor at Atelier Bauermeister, 1960 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Christo and Jeanne-Claude by Wolfgang Volz and Perrin Chernow, 1981-1992 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - Howard Conant by Bruce Davidson and Uncredited, 1957; undated (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Stevan Dohanos by William Noyes, circa 1980 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Sally Drummond, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Nancy Grossman, circa 1980 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Audrey Flack by Jeanne Hamilton, circa 1974 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Duane Hanson, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Barkley Hendricks, 1988 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Paul Jenkins, circa 1980 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Lester Johnson by Bob Ellison, circa 1968 (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Takeshi Kawashima by Vernon L. Smith, circa 1995 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Nicholas Krushenick, circa 1980 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Ben Mamoud by William Noyes, circa 1980 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Harry McCormick, circa 1990 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Joyce Stillman Myers, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - Reuben Nakian, circa 1986 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Alice Neel, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Louise Nevelson by William Noyes, circa 1980 (Box 22, Folder 35)
      Pictured with Nevelson in one photograph is Arne Glimcher. Oversized photograph in box 23.
    - Gabor Peterdi, 1960; 1980 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Claes Oldenburg by Harry Shunk, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Irving Sabo, circa 1980 (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Levon West, circa 1950 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Francisco Zuñiga by Ariel Zuñiga, 1979-1982 (Box 22, Folder 40)
  - Photographs of Others, circa 1965-1988 (Box 22, Folder 41)
    Includes photographs of Robert Doty, Michael A. Croman, Theodore Bikel, Sonny Costanzo, and unidentified subjects.
  - Photographs of Artwork (Box 22)
    - Bust of Burt Chernow, circa 1997 (Box 22, Folder 42)
    - Photocollages by Burt Chernow, circa 1990; circa 1997 (Box 22, Folder 43)
  - Oversized Photograph from Box 21, Folder 40 (Box 23)
  - Oversized Contact Sheet from Box 21, Folder 48 (Box 23)
  - Oversized Contact Sheets from Box 21, Folder 49 (Box 23)
  - Oversized Photograph from Box 22, Folder 12 (Box 23)
  - Oversized Photograph from Box 22, Folder 20 (Box 23)
  - Oversized Photograph from Box 22, Folder 30 (Box 23)
  - Oversized Photograph from Box 22, Folder 35 (Box 23)